iransportspress.com 2004-06-06

# Iran Sports Press(www.iransportspress.com)

Since we were founded, Iran Sports Press has tried to help its visitors and community members retain their privacy while they take advantage of all the Internet has to offer. We are committed to protecting your privacy and developing technology that gives you the safest and most powerful online experience that you can get anywhere. If you have questions about this, please write us at [admin@iransportspress.com](mailto:webmaster@iransportspress.com)

Iran Sports Press will notify you:

  1. What personally identifiable information of yours or third party personally identification is collected from you through the web site
  2. The organization collecting the information
  3. How the information is used
  4. With whom the information may be shared
  5. What choices are available to you regarding collection, use and distribution of the information
  6. The kind of security procedures that are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under Iran Sports Press control 
  7. How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information. 

If you feel that we are not abiding by its posted privacy policy, you should first contact Iran Sports Press by [webmaster@iransportspress.com](mailto:webmaster@iransportspress.com)

Iran Sports Press is the sole owner of the information collected on this site.  We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement.  Iran Sports Press collects information from our users at several different points on our website.  

**Registration**  
In order to use the ISP Discussion Forum, a user must first complete the registration form.  During registration a user is required to give their contact information (such as name and email address).  This information is used to contact the user about the services on our site for which they have expressed interest.

**Cookies**  
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s hard drive containing information about the user.  Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site.  Once the user closes their browser, the cookie simply terminates.  For instance, by setting a cookie on our site, the user would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site.  If a user rejects the cookie, they may still use our site.  The only drawback to this is that the user will be limited in some areas of our site.  For example, the user will not be able to participate in any of our Sweepstakes, Contests or monthly Drawings that take place. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site.

Some of our business partners use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers).  However, we have no access to or control over these cookies.

Areas of Iran Sports Press using cookies:

  * ISP Discussion Forum - The Iran Sports Press Discussion forum uses cookies and other tracking devices to enhance the security and reliability of the forum. All information collected is purely for security purposes, and at no time will be disclosed to any other parties. The information is used to disable accounts of users that fail to adhere to the rules of the forum. The email addresses submitted by members during registration are solely for registration purposes, and at no time will be disclosed to any parties. 
  * Inter@active Page - Use of cookies to enhance the accuracy of the polls.

**Log Files**  
We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use.   IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

**Sharing  
**We will share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person.

**Links  
**This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we Iran Sports Press are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites.  We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information.  This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

**Surveys & Contests  
**From time-to-time our site requests information from users via surveys or contests.  Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information.  Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code, age level).  Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes.  Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site.

**Security  
**This website takes every precaution to protect our users’ information.  When users submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and off-line. 

When our registration/order form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number and/or social security number), that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry - SSL.  While on a secure page, such as our order form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to un-locked, or open, when you are just ‘surfing’. 

While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user-information off-line.  All of our users’ information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices.  Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our billing clerk or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information.  Our employees must use password-protected screen-savers when they leave their desk.  When they return, they must re-enter their password to re-gain access to your information.  Furthermore, ALL employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices.  Every quarter, as well as any time new policies are added, our employees are notified and/or reminded about the importance we place on privacy, and what they can do to ensure our customers’ information is protected.  Finally, the servers that we store personally identifiable information on are kept in a secure environment, behind a locked cage. 

If you have any questions about the security at our website, you can send an email to [webmaster@iransportspress.com](mailto:webmaster@iransportspress.com).

**Supplementation of Information  
**In order for this website to properly fulfill its obligation to our visitors, it is necessary for us to supplement the information we receive with information from 3rd party sources.

For example, to determine if our customers qualify for one of our credit cards, we use their name and social security number to request a credit report.  Once we determine a user’s credit-worthiness, this document is destroyed. 

(or)

In order for this website to enhance its ability to tailor the site to an individual’s preference, we combine information about the purchasing habits of users with similar information from our partners, Company Y & Company Z, to create a personalized user profile.  When a user makes a purchase from either of these two companies, the companies collect and share that purchase information with us so we can tailor the site to our users’ preferences.

**  
Special Offers  
**We send all new members a welcoming email to verify password and username. Established members will occasionally receive information on products, services, special deals, and a newsletter. Out of respect for the privacy of our users we present the option to not receive these types of communications. Please see our choice and opt-out below.

**  
Site and Service Updates  
**We also send the user site and service announcement updates. Members are not able to un-subscribe from service announcements, which contain important information about the service. We communicate with the user to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to their account via email or phone.

**Notification of Changes  
**If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our Homepage so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it.  If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an email.  Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected. 

Please contact [webmaster@iransportspress.com](mailto:webmaster@iransportspress.com) if you have any questions.
